oony.co.in 2016-05-06

# Privacy Policy | Oony

As a user of Oony, you have the right to know how we handle the information we gather when you visit our site [http://oony.co.in](http://oony.co.in/)

## CONSENT

By providing any kind of personal information, you are deliberately choosing to:

Accept all the terms and conditions included in this Privacy Policy. Agree that all the information you have provided can be stored, managed, and be treated for any of the ends herein established. To grant OONY the authorization to compile, store, and utilize such information in any way and fashion, according to the conditions stated in this Privacy Policy and by applicable laws. You acknowledge and comprehend that all the provided information is valid and real. If you wish to verify, modify or complement such information in any way, we request you log in using your username and password. If you have any questions or comments, or if you wish your personal information to be erased from our servers, please get in contact with us to the following e-mail address:[support@oony.com](mailto:support@oony.com)

## Personal Data Recollection and Combination

The main objective of the information compiled by OONY is to offer every user an amiable, efficient experience that matches his or her preferences. OONY only compiles the necessary information to comply with the purposes of its service, and does not process such information in any way that isn’t compatible with the purpose it was compiled for, or authorized by the user. OONY compiles personal information provided by the user during the sign up process, which includes name, e-mail address, postal address, gender, shopping preferences, etc. OONY may also occasionally compile information about the user’s usage preferences (such as geographic location, images or objects selected clicked or selected during the user’s visit to our website or e-mail message) to be used internally for service improvement and research. OONY may also store information provided by the user with her express knowledge, such as her response to contact forms, recommendations, new stores suggestions, and e-mails sent to our website. OONY may use such information internally for tasks included in, but not limited to, optimization of the service in all of its features, the addition of new functionalities, etc. Information that has been inputted by or compiled from every user can be combined with the information inputted or obtained from other users to determine goals and demographics for advertising and marketing purposes.

## User Information Update

OONY offers the possibility to review, and modify the information you have provided when signing up to our service. You may change your registration information by logging into OONY’s website, and selecting the ‘Edit Profile’ option relative to the information you wish to modify. You, as a user, have the obligation to keep your personal information up to date.

## Personal Information Protection

Unless solicited by you, or previously accorded with you, OONY’s website shall not share any personal information you provide with third party companies or individuals. In spite of this, you expressly authorize OONY to share your personal information in the following cases: +When It is required by law or by a judicial order. +With companies or people of our trust, for the information to be processed in our behalf, according to our instructions, and respecting this Privacy Policy’s outlines, as well as +the proper confidentiality and security measures. +With government agencies, related to criminal investigations, fraud prevention, or other legal procedures, or if OONY considers it reasonable to protect OONY, its website, its users, or the general public. Unless you explicitly specify otherwise, you authorize OONY to communicate with you to provide information about services or other activities or propositions that may be of your interest.

If you wish to contact us, you may do so to the following e-mail address: [support@oony.com](mailto:support@oony.com). Every time you receive communication on our behalf, you will be given the possibility to remove yourself from our communications listing. In the same way, any individual user can exercise her right to access, rectify, or delete his personal information, by the means of a written petition directed at the following e-mail address: [support@oony.com](mailto:support@oony.com).

## Use and Disclosure of Gathered Information

All the information stored by OONY is considered confidential, and will not be shared with third parties that are not related to the relationship. OONY will be able to share the results of the statistical analysis of the sum of the whole information provided by users for marketing and advertising purposes. If you oppose such usage for any particular reason, you may inform us so through any of our communication channels, or cancel your subscription to our service. Sponsors, advertisers and people outside of OONY will not have access to your personal information in any way or method that may allow them to identify you through the usage of our services. However, OONY assumes no obligation or liability over any information you provide directly or indirectly to third party companies or individuals. Every change, amendment or suppression of your personal information must be communicated to OONY directly, as those changes or amendments will not be shared with or by third parties. You are accountable for the veracity of the information you provide. OONY reserves the right to exclude or ban from its services any user who provides fake information, and to initiate the corresponding legal proceedings.

## SECURITY

OONY commits itself to comply with its obligation to keep secret any personal information provided by the users, and to its duty to treat them as confidential, taking the proper technical, organizational, and security measures in order to prevent their alteration, loss, treatment or unauthorized access. However, in light of the current state of technology, we are in no condition to guarantee an unauthorized access will never occur.

## Information Practices Related to Minors Under 13

If you are under 13 years of age, you must not provide any personal information that identifies you in this site without the proper and explicit consent or permission from your parents or legal guardians. If we become aware that you are under 13, we won’t keep or use any of your personal information in any way without the verifiable consent of your parents or legal guardians, unless it is permitted by law. That information will only be used to get in contact with your parents or legal guardians, and to notify them about the participation of a child on our website, or to get their approval for such participation.

## CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

You accept that the conditions in this policy govern the usage of any information collected while it is still in force. OONY reserves the right to change this policy at any time, with such changes entering in effect at the very moment they are published in this website.

## DATA INTEGRITY

OONY processes personal information for the purposes it was compiled, and according to the terms established in this agreement only. OONY verifies its data compilation, storage, and processing practices regularly in order to ensure it is only compiling, storing and processing the necessary personal information to provide a better service. OONY takes all reasonable measures to assure the personal information it processes is precise, complete, and current, but it is up to the users to update, or correct their personal information when necessary.

## QUESTIONS?

If you have any questions or comments about our Personal Information practices, or about this Privacy Policy, please be as kind as to communicate with us through the following e-mail address, and we’ll gladly address your comments: [privacy@oony.com](mailto:privacy@oony.com)

This Privacy Policy was last updated in May, 2014.
